Hello there!
Welcome to Elf Garden!
- So many smells!
- Reservation under Tonome.
Of course.
For the original blend
tasting experience?
I'll show you to your seats.
Think about the kind of tea you'd like,
and pick out your leaves.
What kind of tea do
you like, Tonome-san?
I tend to focus on
the effects they advertise.
Teas that improve your focus
or help you to relax.
- What about you?
- Let me think.
I really loved the one
you made for me before!
That makes me happy.
Hey, I came up with that blend myself!
Your boy here came by the shop before!
He said, "I want something
that'll make my girl happy."
You're a lucky gal!
C'mon, spill! What's it feel like
to date an invisible man?
Have you been dating long?
Is it serious? You guys cohabiting?
I wouldn't say we're
officially dating just yet...
Just yet, you say?
So it's going to happen soon?
Maybe tonight's the big night?
- Ow!
- Please excuse my idiot husband!
I'm being oppressed by a white elf!
Pipe down, dark elf!
Erm...
I'm sorry. That was a bit awkward.
Well, as long as we're here...
I'd like you to make a tea blend for me.
Of course I will.
I'll make one for you, too!
I can't wait to try it.
I'll make it worth the wait!
I totally made this happen!
Check that ego.
All right. I'll brew tea from
the blends you created.
Wasn't putting the tea together fun?
Yes, I look forward to drinking it.
I-I was wondering...
Did you find this shop just for me?
Did you do research for that?
I'm sorry! I got carried away speculating!
Please forgive me!
You're right on the money.
I-I'm sorry!
I have a habit of trying
to work out people's motivations.
You have excellent intuition.
It's a fantastic quality
in a detective's assistant.
I-It's not that impressive.
There are so many things I don't know.
About you, too...
I can't even imagine what you look like
unless I touch you, so...
Want to touch me?
- My hand, of course.
- Y-Yes.
Go ahead.
Your fingers are more slender
than my father's.
Your nails are well kept, too.
Even if people can't see them,
I try to maintain good hygiene.
Still, I'm glad.
I can't see how well
kept they are for myself.
I understand!
I can't see mine either, so I'm always
worried that they might look strange...
Your nails are very well kept too.
It's like he's the one
who can see right through me...
Here you are.
This was brewed
from the blends you created.
It smells wonderful.
- Let's try them.
- O-Of course!
Jarashi-san.
How does Tonome-san usually dress?
How does he dress?
He wears suits most
of the time, I guess.
What are his suits like?
What subset?
Subset?
I guess... the English gentleman kind?
A gentleman! That sounds very cool.
Yeah, it totally is!
English gentlemen are spies,
and that's super cool!
English gentlemen are spies?!
She's talking about movies.
And of course Tonome
wears suits for his job.
Why are you asking about that?
Well... I was thinking of buying clothing,
and I wanted information for reference...
If you're buying clothes for yourself,
why are you asking about Tonome?
Don't tell me...
You two want to go twinsies?
Hooray!
No, of course not...
She wants an outfit
for their dates, you dumb feline.
- What was that?!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Yes, it's for... dates.
With Tonome?!
Y-Yes.
I get you, Shizuka!
Dressin' up, right?
That's way too far!
Can we please keep this between us?!
We're the only ones
who work here, so yeah.
I've been buying the same kinds
of outfits so I didn't end up
with mismatches.
But... I want special clothing
for special days.
Shizuka! Leave it to me!
I'll be your shopping buddy!
Th-Thank you!
Hey, Jarashi.
You can be pretty overbearing.
Don't push Yako around too much.
You're short-tempered, too.
See?
Yes, yes!
Nice one!
Adorable!
I-Is it?
You usually go girlish
and casual with your outfits.
It'll be handy to have some more mature
things you can wear
to high-class restaurants!
- Try this one on too!
- W-Wait a minute!
I want to confirm what
kind of outfit it is.
Image captured. Cloth is pale blue.
Pale blue...
Shizuka. I'll describe it for you.
Oh, thank you!
This blouse is...
It's got a lively fabric...
What does "lively" mean in this context?
It flows just like hair,
which makes it seem really dynamic.
And...
Sorry. I haven't been
very considerate with you.
Are you worried about what
Kikira-san said to you?
W-Well...
I also almost made you trip
over my bike before, too...
This isn't like you, Jarashi-san!
Is your stomach bothering you?
Don't eat things off the ground!
Hey, you can throw shade too, Shizuka.
Sorry about that.
Okay! When we're done shopping,
I'll take you to my favorite spot!
Yes!
Let's do that!
Speaking of, Kikira-san.
Are there any restaurants you recommend?
Wouldn't know.
Come on, indulge me
in a little conversation.
Rather not.
I see.
I was hoping for some ideas.
Well, back to work.
KIKIRA-SAN
RESTAURANT RECS
I'm grinning.
You don't have to tell me
your expressions, darn it!
Come on in.
Hey, lookie here!
It's our customers!
You're the teahouse owners.
That's right!
I'm Karma!
His wife, Light.
We're a couple of elf spouses!
WAITING ROOM
I see.
Unsavory characters in white hoods?
They sit in a car across the street
from the shop every day.
They've been asking around
the neighborhood about us,
and taking pictures from the car...
That does sound quite unsettling.
Man, in all my hundred years,
I've never had a stalker!
It's so exciting!
Um... you are frightened, right?
They seem to be following
us around as well.
- Did they follow you he—
- No worries! We totally lost them!
They don't know we're here!
I hope he's right.
Understood.
I'll look into the suspects
and think up countermeasures.
Thank you very much.
Hooray!
- Hey, Tonome.
- Yes?
I traced the transmitter
Jarashi stuck on the car
to a big pharma corp in the mountains.
As for the people in the car,
they dress all the same,
but their faces are all different.
This looks like...
This could be pretty dire.
May I ask...
What do you mean by that?
It could be an organized thing.
Beyond simple stalking, then.
Jarashi-san's guarding
them. Let her know—
Tonome, bad news!
A couple of cars stopped
in front of the shop,
and a bunch of men marched out!
I took the lovebirds out the back way,
and we're on the run now!
This is awesome! It's just like a movie!
At least try to be panicked!
Understood. I'm on my way.
There's multiple threats.
I'll head that way, too.
I'll stay here!
Please be careful!
Yako-san, hold down the fort.
Please let them work it out safely...
Come in.
A visitor?
I'm sorry. I'm afraid it's past the
time we accept new clients.
Are you here by yourself?
Yes, why?
Stay away from her.
Tonome-san?
I realized they might target the agency.
N-No!
I'm an elf!
A white elf, just like my daughter!
This is my father. He runs
a pharmaceutical company.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I see. You got worried about your
daughter and wanted to check in on her.
Father, why is the whole clan involved?
And in disguises, at that...
Well, they all wanted to come,
and we didn't want you to notice...
Then you two visited a detective agency,
so we thought there might be
a misunderstanding...
So they did follow you.
Aw, Daddy! Clumsy you!
Keep in mind, I still haven't
given you my blessing, dark elf.
Gotta say, I never asked for it, Daddy!
Stop that!
Would you say that's... case closed?
There are plenty of ongoing issues,
but they're all on their end.
Well done today, everyone.
It's nice to have a drinking party
with my co-workers!
We haven't had many
chances for it, after all.
I just like to get home on time.
What a sourpuss.
I bet you don't get any girls.
I already have a partner,
so I don't need to.
What is it?
I didn't know that!
You've never mentioned it.
Congrats, I guess?
I don't need it!
Actually, I've been wondering.
Shizuka, you don't drink?
I do, but it's harder
to get home if I'm drunk.
It can be dangerous
if I dull my senses too much.
Oh, I get it.
Well, I'll walk you home
this time. Feel free to drink!
A-Are you sure?
Totally!
So, what do you want?
I-Is there anything nice and sweet?
Hey... Jarashi-san?!
Just pathetic.
- What now?
- Yako-san.
I just called you a taxi.
I'll make sure you get there.
Wh-Wh-Wh...
What do I do?!
Should I invite him up for tea?
But is my room even
in any condition for company?!
- Yako-san.
- Yes?!
There's a restaurant I'm interested in.
Could we go there sometime?
They say it's a dark restaurant.
You eat in a pitch-black interior.
Oh! I've heard of that!
I've been interested in seeing
the world you live in.
- What do you think?
- The world I live in?
I shall be your guide through the dark!
I really appreciate that.
Thank you for seeing me back.
Of course. I'll see you tomorrow.
W-Wait...
Would you like to share a cup of tea?!
I don't want to leave the taxi waiting.
Oh, of course!
But if you'd like, I'll happily
come back again sometime.
- Good night.
- Good... night...
I-I've gotta get someone
to review my room for me!
- Yako-san?
- Y-Yes.
You're wearing another
beautiful outfit.
Y-You think so?
I hope you'll guide me through the meal.
I-I'll do my best!
How is it, Tonome-san?
Can you not see anything at all?
Actually, there's
a very faint light right now.
Attention, all!
We will now put out all the lights
and plunge you into true darkness!
Is it pitch black now?
Yes, it is.
Tonome-san, welcome to my world!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Now, you'll want to pat around
and find out where everything is!
Understood.
Tonome-san sounds really nervous.
So good!
Did you try this "terrine" stuff?!
Tonome-san?
I'm sorry. I need to freshen up.
O-Okay.
What's happening?
Yako-san?
Tonome-san.
Would you like to leave?
- Is that all right?
- Of course.
I'm sorry to cut it short
after inviting you out.
That's fine!
We wasted the wonderful food, too.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
Don't worry about that either!
I asked the staff to box it up for us!
Incredible!
- I can't wait to get back and eat it!
- Neither can I.
Would you like to come by my place to eat?
Can I?!
It's all ready.
I arranged it all on one plate.
Oh!
Would you like to drink?
Oh no!
I'm so nervous, all I can say is "Oh!"
Yako-san. I'm sorry
about the trouble today.
That's fine. Don't worry about it.
I didn't realize it, but
I may be afraid of the dark.
The dark?
The only reason I can think of is...
Do you know how they sometimes
hold sleepaway camp for children?
There was this time when they
hosted a test of courage...
We had to hold a candle
and walk up a mountain road.
Hey, it's Kat-chan's team!
Kat-chan!
Wait for me!
Someone...
I thought it would be dangerous to go on,
so I decided to wait
until someone came to get me.
But nobody came.
I gave up on waiting and managed
to make it back to the cabins...
But nobody even realized I was gone.
Because I'm invisible, it's all
the same to them if I'm there or not.
I guess that was
a little traumatic for me.
In the city, you're
rarely in the total dark.
I never realized it
made me uncomfortable,
so it really surprised me.
I'll have to be careful in the future.
Tonome-san.
I notice these things.
Yako-san...
Your sounds are usually so put-together,
so it's easy to tell
when they're flustered.
Even now, you're trying
to sound cheerful, but...
The sounds of your glass and the
rate you're drinking are all scrambled.
I can tell you were really scared and sad.
I'd miss you if you weren't there, though.
I'd definitely look for you!
Will you be my girlfriend?
Ah, is that your reaction?
N-No!
I don't have a problem with it!
Right.
I just realized I like having you nearby.
What do you think?
B-But...
If we're officially dating now,
then what happens next?
Ah... No, no!
I was planning on dropping you off
and coming straight home this time!
"This time"?
Yako-san, please...
Come on.
Or do you want me to do something more?
What is it? You're
speaking in sound effects.
I-It's the sound
of being mentally unprepared!
Yes, I'm sure it is.
Here.
- Squeak!
- I like you.
Don't squeak!
EPISODE 2: THE GREAT DATE PLAN
TO BE CONTINUED